Our stakeholder engagement plan.
You plan stakeholder engagement,
you produce a plan.
So it documents how we're going to engage
the stakeholders.
That's the way we're going to build a
relationships.
Involving, communicating them with them,
engaging them on our project, involving
them in meetings, document how we'll
collaborate with the stakeholders.
the strategy for how resistant
stakeholders can become
supportive or leading,
getting them over to our side.
A lot of times showing the
benefits of your project is the
best way to get people over on
our side to support our project.
It'll document the procedures and
strategies for promoting productive
involvement, engagement of our
stakeholders.
And it contains this stakeholder
engagement assessment matrix.